all other what I say is that no one, you know, the district board of Tulsa County can't
sell somebody in Ottawa County, how they can deal with their car. Only the district
board of Ottawa County can do that. It's like, you know, Oklahoma tries to deal with
your car to deal with their car. You can't do it, you know. No court has that authority. Only
other county district board has that authority. And then there's another question with regards
to attachment, A, which is the legal restriction of the property that is being released
to the voice of girls, but I'm not exactly sure what the question is, but the amount of
land that is being released to the voice of girls, but is a slightly larger amount of land
than what the building itself is going to take. And the reason for that is because the
re-except, and I'm assuming that they expect there's going to be $1,000 going up around the
building so that somebody wouldn't let the car in nearby parking space, then ran into the building.
But that's part of the property that they're taking. And so that's why that's part of that legal restriction.
But I'll go on to say that the whoever was asking the questions suggested that
we put in the agreement that after the building is constructed, that there will still be $3,6,2
parking spaces remaining in that parking lot. According to Travis, the guy that's the most
knowledge about this, and he can't be here at the meeting night because he's being sworn into the
school or business. He says there will be $6,2. It's makes sense. So I have no problems with adding that
to the contract, but I have the agreement that everything is all the construction is done,
that there will still be $6,2. That $3,6,2 parking space is remaining in the parking lot. And with that,
I have the managers, business like good, through all the questions that I was working with,
we're about to speak in and again.
three months, and he's going to be done. I guess I am.
And we'll go a little bit of a little bit of a white.
Peter Parker, I guess, and members, the contract reported
night will be in effect for 40 years.
Our bones will be dust in 264.
The city in Miami will still be dealing with fallout
from the problems this contract is going to create for our journey.
It's terminology clearly demonstrates
that the club is declaring itself a business
with the authority to rent out it to post a new building
for a product as a venue for entertainment units.
Yet his contract calls for the city to grant a list
of financial favors to the new downtown business
in addition to $50,000 annually
in direct financial support.
You add up all the terms that financial favors
in part me, in comes to 108,000,
$200 a year in credits and payments
for the total over 40 years of 4 million,
$320,000.
That the city is getting in financial favors
to this new business.
Even though this business will realize a problem
in return for the relevant downtown family.
In effect, this contract guarantees
the city is going to subsidize this business.
Thus, great in the city, a money that is needed
for such serious purposes as strictly paid.
And no place in this generous contract
that the city will be underwriting
is the order of the department
that this business had an independent annual party.
Here are just a few of the provisions
of this proposed business meeting.
Part A number four admits, as being this pointed out,
the warranty date may have to be decided by courtable.
Part C number 11 says,
unattachment E is intended to be a living document
continuously under modification
to reflect the ever changing environment.
Then, more the terms of this contract are all triggered.
Such a particular way of some of the business
with no prohibition for bringing their website
will change it for the council or vote.
Part C number 13 says,
in the event that the clubs will become bankrupt
and solve the city that terminate the lease
has been pointed out.
The city for the council is that this business
operating under the guidance.
of a nonprofit organization who go under.
And parts of the number 36 has been quarantined out,
includes the statement being exclusive in-view
for any court action shall be the district court in
for honest families of trouble.
This just happens to be the district courts,
beside it over the years, but it's very first
in these the current president of the court.
Thank you.
That's by the trial of America.
That's been a great one.
Yes.
Creatorship on behalf of my little Jacob and friends of the colon.
I'd like to speak a little bit to the construction
of the crimes that are attached to this construction experience
for over 39 years.
There's a 1.5 million grant in the strangest tube
of this entity to build this,
whatever they want to do with this,
and the current trial is the current project
of my estimation.
It is probably going to end up being at 1.8 to 1.9 million.
An estimate for years and years.
So the remaining short of the money there,
may have to think about how to do much of that shortly.
Also, the timeline, the leader is a time limit given.
I think the last thing that we last heard,
at least I last attended the December 2025,
was the deadline to spend this money.
That's probably one of those from now.
And my experience with,
and we don't even have construction projects.
So with that, with the pre-construction of investigations,
the construction experience,
I'm coming within 23 months.
So the residents, the boys and girls
don't have the right advance to the wall,
right at the discipline of the single one.
And I think that's, that's evident.
The other thing I'd like to talk about is the architect.
The little research I've talked about is the,
my daughters and architect,
work with a lot of our attention to the years.
This architect is a racial web,
I don't think Colorado.
She had her website, which I would encourage you all to do.
Some of her sort of web architecture.com.
And look at the website.
She specializes in interior design.
And that's it.
She's not an agricultural site.
She's not an environmental project like this.
This is not a complicated project.
But she may or may not be really giving
to the people who want to build a school of accurate information
on costs, about time months.
And that's sort of that.
I think that's a consideration to do look at it.
The other thing I want to talk about is this,
this project.
And I've said this before.
It seems to have happened.
curler a lot of options and sometimes you interrupt goes into like, and I just didn't
bite through this and confidence because this is, I mean, life is hard. Sometimes those
obstacles can be fences to protect from doing all the things. And I think that's something
that we need to look at. I still think this is a sport day and you fit around home. If you use
a big enough hand, you can make that sport day fit. You can't get it up. If you have a, if you
have a route day that fits my home, you would get it in your work, you can move it a bit easily.
I feel like that this is something that it's time to go. It's a crisis for the boys and girls
club, but not necessarily crisis. I want to tell you a true story. My husband and I have
him on property in the Northeast part of town for 29 years. And we had a neighbor at one time who's
backfans backed up to our property and they decided to build swimming pool and they wanted to also
have a concrete walkway and I saw a bit. However, we format that they can count and fit in their backyard.
So, they decided to move their fence. They moved their fence, 20 feet onto our property,
onto our pasture. No permission, no regular for ownership, or what a good cost the owners,
her response, the woman when we went found out, I'm doing it. Well, you have a lot of property,
this is what she told me. You have a lot of property, but we need some of it. So, we have something
we've got to do with our fence and we're going to take you to my home. Okay? I think we can go home with
like to say about part of your property for your neighbor, so that that's called going on. And then this could
be just a little bit dramatic too, but you might even go back in your history book to have said,
read about the title tiers and what happens is some property that was just taken. The new start for building
was purchased in a panic and without a contingency clause for property for a gen. I'd reference this
before to a billionaire for a terminal with an out-of-one way. However, there's a wonderful
chance that could do it once away at the seats. That the club has free access to and also.
for the kids to play all kinds of outdoor games like soccer, baseball, soccer, all in the grass.
There's also great playground equipment that all ages like, and transportation should be easy
with all the vehicles belonging to the club.
Poor planning and a lack of due diligence should not constitute a crisis for so many other entities and businesses.
Such as, my own theater, pizza hut, Shawnee Trig, Ryan Slayner, and all the shops
love taking a moment, a long-range street at the moment, the theater itself.
But all of these places are being asked to make any sessions.
This lease agreement is so far from being ready to vote on if the error is ready to vote on.
The city is being manipulated into a total bailout to fix problems
that never should have occurred.
The multitude of demands from the club on the city in this contract for enormous.
And there will be more demands to come.
I am sure of it.
Thank you.
And volunteer to the hours of new ways in my life.
And after years.
We have two reasons.
We want to help bring the economy from the back to my end.
But we also want to make it all the way through certain sessions to work.
We want them to live a lot that we know the students to run out of here.
None of this at any time I've raised this for spending nearly every day at the theater volunteer.
Our motivation is to do a good part of our hotel.
And it might as well be successful.
We can really assist in this part of these initiatives.
Before I became a volunteer, I was teacher at my hospital.
In addition, we know that business in my area.
Others who have so many here tonight, and we'll see.
I've also learned that this is still currently our business owners in my area.
We did not make mistakes.
It has been made in this situation.
As Jane was called now.
There are shunnyness and contingencies that move that contract for some time.
So now we have prices.
We have you all have to make a decision on what to do at this point.
They want to be able to emphasize that 54 by 100 foot gymnasium,
without a deep theater, the called theater.
Which is why.
It's a part of the knowledge engine that drives tax dollars to find out what it shows.
Can't speak to the viewers.
We're going to ask you about the most important part that we have for moving shows and it adds to the out of the door.
So the club can know what's amazing.
But there's a perfectly good jazzy and just three blocks of what it calls it.
And as Jenny pointed out, I got a part which is out of the facility where everybody is free to go.
And it's in walking distance.
Many other issues included in this federal park and this being taken out,
not just by the gym equipment, but by the end of the park and this on the park,
or that in action, which is amazing.
And part of the facility is accessible.
In August, we were asked, our opinion of this entire program by the sitting manager,
to work that whole floor.
And we have a stand since that time, which was August, meaning good day and professionally.
We're praying for great and socially with host or emails that they send out, asking people to weigh in publicly.
And also, we were thrown through the mud base and we said that,
that red dust here, my children are going to want to go along with this.
So we feel like we have the threatened, especially with somebody.
We have lots of hate and...
We're not just losing the parking that the facility is going to sell.
The facility is accessible and we can fire more work.
And according to what I was looking at, and what it says, it's this building home,
to require about 27 parking places, it's sell.
Because this business, the most likely, we have any events from the old Friday, Saturday nights,
as well as the phone, the comment.
I can see a very complicated, I can see big problems happening in the future.
It may not happen yet, but I think it's going to happen to be dangerous.
But the end of this year, the mind of the tower, should be in total of the apartments, which will be 65 apartments,
opening up across the street to the home.
They should require somewhere in a good 50-200 apartment license.
It's going to be very important, but it's just that people are going to be there day-by-day.
So the building itself, according to 200, there are one part of the place where the 200 square feet,
and we have to check that when we do have access to the information I don't have,
but it's like to make it a gymnasium in large, one part of the place where the 200 square feet are four days.
You know, my name has a girl for the last one years.
We should have to be with my family in five.
My name has been to a 40-year recession.
In the last few years, my family should be some sparks of brittle.
Thanks to people like you guys that are building and making my efforts grow and doing things that helps to grow.
And we're trying to do everything that we can to make mine grow also.
And become the private candidate that wants to work and do anything greater.
But recognizing this valuable part in places, and they are still there.
Because when we think of more places, a little time, we've got to go out and tear down houses.
We've got to tear down buildings, and they're very expensive to replace.
So anyway, he's very important in places.
In places that we're working with, and at the same time, increasing the need to remove,
I mean, is not the extent of the right direction.
To occur more pain, retail, businesses, and customers in a downtown shopping industry.
So please say that.
Thank you all for letting us speak, appreciate it, and appreciate you guys for watching.
We've got to say something sometimes, sometimes we're talking about something else.
So I want to speak just a minute to take you away from that earlier.
If you want to slightly duck in a class like a duck, it's probably a duck.
This law was mislead with C5 to a long time.
You know, it's a C1 line.
It's for off-street parking.
That's the way it was originally intended.
That's the way it's always been.
And so we wanted to revisit the warrant of D, which then also talked about.
And when we first wrote that stuff, the rule was known about this D.
And in section one, it says, one of the respect to the covenants of this property is a building that's off-street parking.
The only reference to an exploration is in section two.
Which terms does not apply to the covenants section one.
Now, the attorney that was enlisted to upgrade this, only mentioned section two, he mentioned section one at all.
And that's sort of strict accompaniment for a true name and soft string part of his.
Two of the attorneys disagreed with what the opinions have been given.
And we also had two other attorneys that we have hired to actually look to it in depth.
Going back away back into the honey of this and with any very issues we need on this.
The, the talking about parking spots, which are at the day of his interview,
he alluded to the National Park and the Bill Cancer Institute, which, I looked at it, got in the day,
and said those parking spots are very, very worthwhile, the worth a lot, and they're very important.
And in fact, just to give you a couple words from him, he says people are moving back to smaller cities, a lot of the idea of a great downtown area,
just like the ones you have to soak and definitely get into creating it.
It's just needing to see people downtown.
We look forward to future road.
With that in mind, we want to say a concept throughout the NFL of small cities.
It's passenger cars and parking is so important.
The average parking spot is worth $4,500 to $5,000, so given away $12,000,
like the Lundies, the strange ones around here is a gift of over $60,000.
The revenue that is generated per parking spot is over $20,000 to here, $20,000 to here.
If you think about that amount of money, let's spot the Lundies and the stakes that we're losing,
$65 to $100 in this lot of money and what's out there.
And we're going to need more.
If we plan the road, we're going to need more.
So, the parking spots are very valuable.
We need more, not less.
And I just appreciate you all.
And no, this decision's going to be tough.
And I know the mayor is one of the best areas.
We've got to the monument and we're all one monument to the road in prosper.
And so, I appreciate you all very much.
And we can see our city and the manager.
Thank you.
That's one brick board.
Good evening, Mayor Parker.
It's a council lot of like to.
Thank you for giving me the opportunity to speak tonight.
My name is Brent Ford.
I'm a vice president, a mind-blowing leader.
And they've asked me to represent them tonight.
Let me first start out by saying that we think what the girls love does is wonderful thing.
We support evening in the edge of the gates and towers and instills confidence in the young people of our community.
Our organization as well as a great many kids and teams that are a wonderful part of our professions.
And our summer workshop in the U.S.
This is quite amazing to watch you grow up to the years in their scale, their confidence, and their ability.
speed in front of large crowds.
My little theater and the golden theater, while there are separate entities, they are very
closely intertwined.
We do five play with small musicals each year, and all of those take place on the golden stage.
Our buildings are also right next to one another.
My amazes is also so very fortunate to have the golden theater.
There are many, many towns of our size, and even much larger communities who would give
anything to have such a treasure.
The Golden draws many thousands of people from all over the world and from around our country
into our community, to see a unique architecture and experience of its wonderful history.
In addition to that, many more thousands of years come from Oklahoma and the surrounding
states, to enjoy concerts, to very next all kinds, and see the place and musicals that
I am a little theater, put on.
On top of all of these visitors, it is also host to a number of festivals, local school,
migrant, and man concerts, and many other activities to the University of Maine.
In addition to the crowds, the attendance of the 12th, the Miami downtown also draws large crowds
for other units, such as the Route 666 Heritage Fest, designed a lot of Google Hop, and the
Christmas parade just to name a few.
Furthermore, there are other ideas in the plants for the downtown that are being pursued right now,
that would draw even more people into the downtown area.
To my advice, let me just say that we are not removing any part of the downtown.
If anything, we should be discussing adding part of it.
Parting people's access, access is already difficult to many business downtown, and to many of
the events I have mentioned here tonight.
If you would like to see a decline in attendance to all of these, many wonderful things downtown,
but the first step is to make access harder by eliminating part of it.
The loss of parking behind our building would no doubt have direct any of the impacts on
my little theater and a little theater, especially for our building patrons, but it would also
have an any impact on the entirety of the downtown.
Currently, my little theater is looking to add a sign on the back of our building to advertise
our opening shows.
This plan to build the gymnasium with a completely blocked career of our building.
We would simply ask the city council workers in the interests of the city and the city's access.
Thank you, Relay.
The closing of our public speaking, again, all of us are, we're going to read to be down to the staff
room for a technical session, the technical session will allow me to do for the theater, then to
do the interior of the city manager hire.
So, we'll be in a moment and come out, so that's what we wanted by hanging out, I don't know if that
will last time.
We need to make this happen for a bigger place.